psocial.in 2013-11-16

# Interest Based Social Networking Site, India | Share Images & Videos - sotialize.com

The sotialize.com privacy **policy was** first published and made effective on 10th September 2012

Unless otherwise defined in this Policy, terms used in this Policy have the same meanings as in our sotialize.com Terms of Service, accessible at **http://www.sotialize.com/terms**. As used in this Policy, the terms “using” and “processing” information include using cookies on a computer, subjecting the information to statistical or other analysis and using or handling information in any way, including, but not limited to collecting, storing, evaluating, modifying, deleting, using, combining, disclosing and transferring information within our organization or among our affiliates within India.

sotialize.com is the corporate name for sotialize.com . In this Policy, we will refer to sotialize.com as “sotialize.com”, “we”, “our” or “us.”

In this Terms & Services agreement the name sotialize.com is a brand owned by Digital e Brandz Private Limited (DEB Pvt Ltd). So the name sotialize.com & DEB Pvt Ltd is and means the same thing.

This policy is provided to you to inform you of our policies and procedures. This policy may be modified from time to time at our sole discretion. 

**We collect information in the following ways:**

a. We collect information that you voluntarily provide to become a registered User of our Service, and when you use aspects of our Service 

b. We collect information when you register to join sotialize.com by logging into an account that you already have with certain third-party social networking sites (“SNS”).

When you browse or use our Service, tools including “Log Data” and “Cookies” collect certain information.

**How we use what we collect:**

Personal: In order to become our registered user we ask few personal Information which may include, but is not limited to, your name, gender, profile photo, biography, location/hometown, website and email address. 

If you create your User account by logging into a SNS via the Service, you are using the Personal Information you have already provided to the SNS (such as your “real” name, email address and other information you make publicly available via the SNS) to create your User account on our Service; the information we collect may depend on the privacy settings you have with the SNS, so please consult the SNS’s privacy and data practices. For example, by using Facebook Connect, you are allowing sotialize.com to access the Personal Information in your Facebook account pursuant to the Facebook Terms of Use regarding your use of the Service via Facebook. 

We use your Personal Information to provide the Service to you. For example:

**Account registration:**  We create your User account for your use of the Service based upon the Personal Information you provide.

**Communication:**  We use your Personal Information to contact you with sotialize.com newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications.

**Customer service:**  We use your Personal Information to respond to your questions and/or inquiries.

**Finding friends:**  You also have the option to import your personal contacts (including email addresses of friend lists via SNS) to the Service so that you can find your friends on the Service, and your friends can find you on the Service.

**Cookies:** A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer or mobile device’s hard disk. Like many online services, sotialize.com uses “cookies” on our Service to collect information. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize “persistent” cookies to save your login information for future logins to the Service. Second, we utilize “session ID” cookies to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage by sotialize.com users and web traffic routing on the Service.

**Sharing of your information**

**sotialize.com Users:**  When you register through the Service and submit Personal Information to create a profile or visual collection, other sotialize.com users will see your name. sotialize.com users will see such additional Personal Information, including, but not limited to, your photo, location, website and biography. Providing additional Personal Information is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with sotialize.com users. We recommend you not to provide confidential information. ****

**Aggregate Information:**  Only non-personal information will be shared with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling and other purposes. 

**Service Providers:**  We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related or to assist us in analysing how our Service is used. The third parties may have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Social Networking Sites:**  We may share the information in your sotialize.com account (including your Personal Information) with the SNSs that you have linked to your sotialize.com account. These third parties have access to your Personal Information for this purpose.

**Facebook Connect and Twitter.**   We allow users to link their Facebook and twitter accounts to sotialize.com. You are free to change this setting.

**Compliance to Law Enforcement:**  sotialize.com abides with the government laws and regulations and may divulge your personal information to them if required by the officials in concern. 

**Business Transfers:**  sotialize.com may sell, divest, transfer, assign, share or otherwise engage in a transaction that involves, some or all of our assets, including any or all of the information described in this Policy, in the course of a corporate divestiture, merger, acquisition, joint venture, bankruptcy, dissolution, reorganization, or any other similar transaction or proceeding.

### Your choices regarding information

You have several choices regarding the use of information on our Service:

**Email Communications:**  If you don’t wish to receive email communications from us, kindly unsubscribe for the service. 

**Cookies:**  If you don’t wish to accept cookies from our service, kindly do so by changing the browser setting.

**De-Linking SNS:**   If you wish to de-link your SNS account (ex: Facebook, twitter) linked with sotialize.com, then you can do so in the preferences section

**Changing or Deleting Your Information:**  All Users may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their User account (including any imported contacts) by contacting us or by editing their profile via the Service. If you completely delete all of your Personal Information, then your User account may become deactivated. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to honour your request. We may retain an archived copy of your records as required by law or for legitimate business purposes

### Links to other sites and services

Our service contains links to third party websites. Note that if you choose to visit the third party websites by clicking on the link, they may place their own cookies or other files on your computer and collect data. 

### How we store and protect information

**Information Security:**  We take your security very seriously. However we do not guarantee that the information you have provided to us may be accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed by any unauthorized persons.

**Phishing:**  Our top priority is to safeguard your identity. Hence we do not request your information in a non-secure way.

**Breach Notification:**  Any breach to your personal information will be notified to you as early as possible.

**International Transfer:**  It is possible that your personal information is stored outside your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction

**Policy information towards Children**

We do not encourage children under 13 to use our service. If a parent becomes aware that their child has submitted their personal information, he or she should contact us for removal.
